You were here
I needed some fresh air
I thought
you were smoking
I don't smoke
That's unexpected
Why?
Do I look like a bad guy
who drinks and smokes?
I just…
You're not denying
My grandma passed away
of lung cancer
so I hate cigarettes
Keep this in mind
as a boyfriend
I felt tension between
Hyobum and you earlier
Weren't you guys close
when in the same group?
No
It was just a business
relationship
Business…
It's the same as ours
Why do you think so?
I'm already
falling for you
I haven't heard
your answer yet
Answer for what?
You know what I mean
Do whatever you want
It's your choice
to like me or not
Let's keep up
the good work! Cheers!
- Go for it!
- Cheers!
Huh? Where's Soobin?
You've always
been together
He can't drink today
He removed his teeth